Marcos Moran

Creative Applications Developer

Email | Linkedin | Portfolio

Barcelona, CAT

SUMMARY

I am a multidisciplinary developer with a passion for creating visually rich interactive experiences. I pride myself on my versatility and like to be involved in both **design and development**. I have experience creating XR applications, ranging from **VR** centered experiences made with Unity 3D, to creating **Augmented Reality** web applications using WebGL.

EXPERIENCE

ANTILOOP Studios -Creative Software Developer

Jan 2020 - October 2020

Antiloop studios is a creative agency focused on creating immersive and interactive applications, as part of marketing campaigns for large scale businesses. I had the chance to work with companies such as **BMW**, **Intel**, **Seat**, **Mini**, **Advance**, and **museums**. As a creative developer, I was in charge of managing my own projects whilst also collaborating on larger scale projects with the rest of the team.

My projects usually involved:

- **Researching** possible technologies/hardware that would be best suited for the experience.
- Planning the User Experience and design of applications.
- **Developing and testing** new features to integrate into the applications.

Freelancer — *Content Creator*

Feb 2018 - Present

As a freelancer, I create content for customers all around the world, these include: music videos, websites, promotional content, and posters.

EDUCATION

Computer Science (BSc Hons)— First Class Honours

University Of Hertfordshire | Sep 2014 - July 2018

Video Game Design and Development

TecnoCampus | Sep 2016 - July 2017

SKILLS

Programming

Unity 3D / C# Javascript/Three.js HTML/CSS Java/Processing

Design

Photoshop After Effects Premiere Pro Illustrator Cinema 4D

Misc

SparKAR TouchDesigner Resolume Raspberry Pi

AWARDS

User Experience Award Received for achieving the highest overall grade in module User Experience.

Best Final Year Project(Runner up) Achieved for developing an Audio Reactive Visualiser Game.